Guide to the Douglas Menuez Photography Collection MSS.PHOTO.0451
Dept. of Special Collections & University Archives
- Series 8. Accession 2011-132, 47.5 Linear feet
  - Subseries 1. Jobs
    - D.M. Selects Champion Italy 1998 Fall Catalog Marci Moriconi May 1998 (Kids) (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - Champion Italy 2/98 (98.3.14) 39653-39706 (Box 87, Folders 8-9)
    - Champion Italy 2/98 (98.3.16) 39543-39608 (Box 87, Folders 10-11)
    - Champion Italy 2/98 (98.3.16) 39543-39608 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Dupont Miracles of Science Campaign Hong Kong Aug. 99 DM Selects 99.23.1 (Box 88, Folders 2-3)
    - Dupont Miracles of Science Campaign Hong Kong Aug. 99 DM Selects 99.23.1 (New Territories: Field) (Box 88, Folders 4-5)
    - Dupont/Menuez Pictures House #1 12:30 P.M. 8/27/99 (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - Dupont/Menuez Pictures House #3 1:20 P.M. 8/26/99 (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - Dupont/Menuez Pictures House #4 7:00 P.M. 8/25/99 (Box 88, Folder 8)
    - Dupont/Menuez Pictures House #5 3:30 P.M. 8/27/99 (Box 88, Folder 9)
    - Dupont/Menuez Pictures House #6 12:00 P.M. 8/30/99 (Box 88, Folder 10)
    - Dupont/Menuez Pictures House #7 1:00 P.M. 8/30/99 (Box 88, Folder 11)
    - Dupont/Menuez Pictures House #8 1:30 P.M. 8/30/99 (Box 88, Folder 12)
    - Dupont Miracles of Science Campaign Hong Kong Aug. 99 (99.23.2) (Box 88, Folder 13)
    - Dupont Miracles of Science Campaign Hong Kong Aug. 99 (99.23.2) (New Territories: Town) (Box 88, Folders 14-15)
    - Dupont Miracles of Science Campaign Hong Kong Aug. 99 (99.23.2) (Kowloon Tong) (Box 88, Folder 16)
    - Dupont Miracles of Science Sept. 99 (99.28.1) (Box 88, Folders 17-18)
    - Dupont Miracles of Science Sept. 99 (99.28.1) (Box 89, Folders 1-2)
    - Doug Menuez Dupont 99.28 DM Selects (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Dupont Miracles of Science Sept. 99. (99.28.2) (Box 89, Folders 4-5)
    - Washington Mutual Home Loans Image Library 04_005 Day 1: Home Improvement Sedgwick Rd. April 2004 (Box 89, Folders 6-11)
    - Washington Mutual Home Loans Image Library 04_005 Day 2: School - 8th Grade Sedgwick Rd. April 2004 (Box 90, Folders 1-6)
    - Washington Mutual Home Loans Image Library 04_005 Day 3: School - 5th Grade Sedgwick Rd. April 2004 (Box 90, Folders 7-11)
    - Washington Mutual Home Loans Image Library 04_005 Day 4: School - Chinese Family Sedgwick Rd. April 2004 (Box 91, Folders 1-5)
    - Washington Mutual Home Loans Image Library 04_005 Day 4: School - Chinese Family Sedgwick Rd. April 2004 (Box 91, Folders 6-7)
    - Washington Mutual Home Loans Image Library 04_005 Day 5: Hip Happening Party Sedgwick Rd. April 2004 (Box 91, Folders 8-11)
    - Washington Mutual Home Loans Image Library 04_005 Day 5: Hip Happening Party Sedgwick Rd. April 2004 (Box 92, Folders 1-4)
    - Washington Mutual Home Loans Image Library 04_005 Day 6: Hispanic Family Sedgwick Rd. April 2004 (Box 92, Folders 5-9)
    - Washington Mutual Home Loans Image Library 04_005 Day 6: Hispanic Family Sedgwick Rd. April 2004 (Box 92, Folders 10-11)
    - Washington Mutual Home Loans Image Library 04_005 Day 6: Hispanic Family Sedgwick Rd. April 2004 (Box 93, Folders 1-3)
    - Washington Mutual Home Loans Image Library 04_005 Sedgwick Rd. April 2004 (Box 93, Folders 4-5)
  - Subseries 2. Jobs - Computer Media
    This Subseries consists of 97 CDs that have been removed from Subseries 1. Jobs.
    Access to Collection
    CDs are CLOSED to researchers. Electronic media may require 2-4 to four weeks for reformatting.
    - Metlife, July 1999, 99.20.2 (2 CDs) (Box CM-1, Folder 1)
    - Corbis Image Submission H03_014 Box 1 (11 CDs) (Box CM-1, Folder 2)
    - Corbis Image Submission H03_014 Box 2 (18 CDs) (Box CM-1, Folder 3)
    - Corbis Image Submission H03_014 Box 3 (10 CDs) (Box CM-1, Folder 4)
    - Corbis Stock Submission #3 Submission Paperwork (1 CD) (Box CM-1, Folder 5)
    - Corbis Image Submission H03_014 Box 4 (02_007 DITLO Africa) (1 CD) (Box CM-1, Folder 6)
    - Corbis Image Submission H03_014 Box 4 (02_023 DITLO LA Drug Dealer) (1 CD) (Box CM-1, Folder 7)
    - Corbis Image Submission H03_014 Box 4 (91_100 DITLO Ireland) (1 CD) (Box CM-1, Folder 8)
    - Corbis Image Submission H03_014 Box 4 (94_100 North Pole Expedition) (1 CD) (Box CM-1, Folder 9)
    - Corbis Image Submission H03_014 Box 4 (98_15 Shanghai Bikes) (1 CD) (Box CM-1, Folder 10)
    - Corbis Image Submission H03_014 Box 4 (98_23 SF Airport) (1 CD) (Box CM-1, Folder 11)
    - Corbis Image Submission H03_014 Box 4 (CEO Portraits) (1 CD) (Box CM-1, Folder 12)
    - Corbis Image Submission H03_014 Box 4 (Favellas) (1 CD) (Box CM-1, Folder 13)
    - Corbis Image Submission H03_014 Box 4 (The Grateful Dead) (1 CD) (Box CM-1, Folder 14)
    - Corbis Image Submission H03_014 Box 4 (H00_089 Stock Car Races) (1 CD) (Box CM-1, Folder 15)
    - Corbis Image Submission H03_014 Box 4 (H01_008 The Basques) (1 CD) (Box CM-1, Folder 16)
    - Corbis Image Submission H03_014 Box 4 (H01_009 Ethiopia) (1 CD) (Box CM-1, Folder 17)
    - Corbis Image Submission H03_014 Box 4 (97_102 One Digital Day) (1 CD) (Box CM-1, Folder 18)
    - Corbis Image Submission H03_014 Box 4 (H01_010 Brazil) (1 CD) (Box CM-1, Folder 19)
    - Corbis Image Submission H03_014 Box 4 (Various Celebrities) (1 CD) (Box CM-1, Folder 20)
    - Corbis Image Submission H03_014 Box 4 (Extra Copies) (22 CDs) (Box CM-1, Folder 21)
    - Corbis Image Submission H03_014 Box 5 (Willis & Geiger 98_25) (1 CD) (Box CM-1, Folder 22)
    - Corbis Image Submission H03_014 Box 5 (99_3 Prince of Persia) (1 CD) (Box CM-2, Folder 1)
    - Corbis Image Submission H03_014 Box 5 (99_5 Cisco) (1 CD) (Box CM-2, Folder 2)
    - Corbis Image Submission H03_014 Box 5 (99.2 Altro Health) (3 CDs) (Box CM-2, Folder 3)
    - Corbis Image Submission H03_014 Box 5 (99.29 Petstore.com) (3 CDs) (Box CM-2, Folder 4)
    - Corbis Image Submission H03_014 Box 5 (00_017 Hallmark Test) (1 CD) (Box CM-2, Folder 5)
    - Corbis Image Submission H03_014 Box 5 (00_018 Hallmark) (2 CDs) (Box CM-2, Folder 6)
    - Hitachi Doremus Advertising January 2000 (00.2 DM Selects) (1 CD) (Box CM-2, Folder 7)
    - Compaq FCB November 2000 (00.103.01) (2 CDs) (Box CM-2, Folder 8)
    - Cisco Systems Inc. Goldberg Moser O'Neil August 2000 (00.67.0) (1 CD) (Box CM-2, Folder 9)
    - Beringer GMO/Hill Holliday March 2001 (01_006) (1 CD) (Box CM-2, Folder 10)
    - Beringer GMO/Hill Holliday March 2001 (01_006) (1 CD) (Box CM-2, Folder 11)
- Series 9. Accession 2012-123, 1.0 folder(s)
  This Series consists of one folder of 35mm slides.
  - Slides (Box 93, Folder 6)